National Women's Health Network records SSC.MS.00360
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES XIV. SUBJECT AND REFERENCE FILES
  - Substance abuse
    - Tobacco, 1978-99, n.d. (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Tranquilizers, 1978-85 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-86, n.d. (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Surgery, 1977-82, n.d. (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Tampons, 1960-79, n.d. (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Tampons and toxic shock syndrome, 1960-89, n.d. (Box 235, Folder 2-3)
  - Teenage pregnancy
    - Informed consent, 1983-85, n.d. (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-85, n.d. (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Teenage women, 1977-99, n.d. (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - Urinary tract infections, 1981-88, n.d. (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Vaginal yeast infections, 1991 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Violence against women
    - Domestic violence, 1976-84, n.d. (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Incest and child abuse, 1979-85, n.d. (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Rape, 1975-85, n.d. (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-85, n.d. (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - Ward, Yolanda, 1980 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Women and health care
    - Kennedy hearings, 1979-84 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-97, n.d. (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Women federal employees, 1979 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Women and the practice of medicine, 1977-92, n.d. (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Women prisoners, 1978-80, n.d. (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Women's health providers, 1978-80, n.d. (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Women's organizations and health centers
    - American Mother Magazine, 1981 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Berkeley Women's Health Center, 1977 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Boston Women's Book Collective (Our Bodies, Ourselves), 1977-81, n.d. (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Bread and Roses Women's Health Center, 1979-82, n.d. (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - California Women's Health Network, 1989 (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Women's Feminist Women's Health Center, 1981-82, n.d. (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - Coalition for the Medical Rights of Women, 1979-82, n.d. (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - Committee for Abortion Rights and Against Sterilization Abuse, 1980-82 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Elizabeth Blackwell Health Center for Women, 1978-86, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Emma Goldman Clinic for Women, 1978, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Feminist Health Fund, 1982-83 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Feminist Women's Health Center
      - Los Angeles, CA, 1978-85, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Oakland, CA, 1981, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Tallahassee, FL, 1979-80, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Gainesville Women's Health Center, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles County Women's Medical Association, 1981-86 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Maryland Commission for Women, 1981 (Box 238, Folder 10)
    - Massachusetts Childbearing Rights Alliance, 1981 (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - Maternity Defense Fund, 1982 (Box 238, Folder 12)
    - Memphis Center for Reproductive Health, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 13)
    - Memphis Feminist Digest, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 14)
    - National Foundation for Women's Health, 1979-80, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 15)
    - Portland Women's Health Center, 1980-83 (Box 238, Folder 16)
    - Preterm Center for Reproductive Health, 1981-82 (Box 238, Folder 17)
    - Washington Women's Self Help, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1919-89, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 19)
  - Workplace discrimination
    - Coalition for the Reproductive Rights of Workers, 1979-82 (Box 238, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous. 1979-85, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 21)
  - X-rays, 1974-80, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-88, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 23)
- SERIES XV. PHOTOGRAPHS AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS [and Computer Media]
  - Photographs
    - Annual report (8), n.d. (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Connerat, Maribelle, n.d. (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Cowan, Belita (4), 1981-83 (Box 239)
    - Dolores, n.d. (Box 239)
    - Driscoll, Shirley, G., n.d. (Box 239)
    - Grant, Dorith, n.d. (Box 239)
    - Harrison, Michelle, 1983 (Box 239)
    - N.H. Feminist Health Center, n.d. (Box 239)
    - NWHN office staff (2), n.d. (Box 239)
    - Reitz, Rosetta, n.d. (Box 239)
    - Seaman, Barbara, n.d. (Box 239)
    - Williams, Ann, n.d. (Box 239)
    - Dalkon Shield press conference (4), 1985 (Box 239)
    - Unidentified groups of women (4), n.d. (Box 239)
    - Unidentified group of women (meeting) (15), 2002 (Box 239)
    - Unidentified (NWHN) women (3), n.d. (Box 239)
    - Unidentified man, n.d. (Box 239)
  - Computer disks
    [These disks cannot be viewed until reformatted]
    - 64 (5.25x5.25), 1980-98 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - 35 (3 1/2),1998-2002 (Box 239)
      This digital media has been copied to NAS. - DB2215
  - Sound recordings
    - Phonograph record (33 1/3) "American Voices" (Public Affairs Broadcast Group), 1983 (Box 239)
    - Audiocassettes
      - Depo-Provera
        - FDA Public Board of Inquiry - Depo-Provera- (Upjohn Company), 1983
          - Testimonies
            - Gena Corea, Charles Anello, Allen Rosenfeld, Solomon Sobel (Box 239, Folder 1)
          - Robert Temple, Vickie Jones, Bruce Stadel, Adrian Gross, Allen Goldman, Robert Hoover, John LaRosa (Box 239, Folder 2-3)
            - Richwald, Gary (Box 239, Folder 4)
            - Sidney Wolfe, Robert Hatcher (Box 239, Folder 5)
            - Gordon Duncan, Paul Stolley, Judith Weisz, Roy Hertz, Griff Ross (Box 239, Folder 6)
            - Marion Valerio, Ronald Gray, Judith Weisz, Gordon Duncan, George Wied (Box 239, Folder 7)
            - Judy Norsigian, Dr. Brenner, Steven Minkin: testimonies and questions (Box 239, Folder 8)
            - Dr. Brent (Box 239, Folder 9)
            - Unidentified (Box 239, Folder 10)
        - Summary (Box 239, Folder 11-12)
      - Population Aid to Developing Countries (Depo-Provera), n.d. (Box 239, Folder 13)
      - Newsmark: For Export Only, n.d. (Box 239, Folder 14)
      - Tamoxifen
        - Bone density and tamoxifen (American Society of Clinical Oncology), 1995 (Box 239, Folder 15)
        - BBC radio tamoxifen prevention trial, 1995 (Box 239, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes
    - Donahue Show (Depo-Provera), 1983 (Box 239)
    - "Assessing Your Risk for Breast Cancer" (Zeneca Pharmaceuticals), n.d. (Box 239)
- OVERSIZED MATERIALS
  - Board of directors orientation: presentation material (1 tube), 1996 (Tube 240)
  - Universal Access: Igniting Our Vision, Setting Our Course: Visioning Session presentation material (3 tubes), 2004 (Tube 241-243)
- SERIES XIV. SUBJECTS AND REFERENCE FILES, 1972-2002; 15.5 linear feet
  The Network's reference files are at the core of this series. It contains mostly printed material on over eighty subjects. These relate to the NWHN's many research projects, legal organizing, and public education campaigns including abortion, birth control and reproductive health, breast cancer, eating disorders, health care reform, menopause, prenatal care, and toxic shock syndrome. It is arranged alphabetically.
- SERIES XV. PHOTOGRAPHS AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS, 1981-2002; 1 linear feet
  This final series contains fifty photographs, ninety-nine floppy disks, one 33 1/3 audio recording, sixteen audiocassettes and two videotapes. The photographs consist of photos used in the Network's annual reports and the office staff. Photographs of individuals include Maribelle Connerat, Belita Cowan, Dorith Grant, Michelle Harrison, Rosetta Reitz, Barbara Seaman, and Ann Williams. In addition there are photographs of the N.H. Feminist Health Center, a DES press conference and twenty-three of groups and individuals that are unidentified. There is a notebook containing 63 5.25" floppy disks and an additional 34 3.5" floppy disks. These disks cover a full spectrum of Network business including publications, employment forms, survey results, and lists. The recording is titled "American Voices" (Public Affairs Broadcast Group). Twelve of the sixteen cassette tapes are from the Depo-Provera FDA Public Board of Inquiry. Ten contain witness testimonies, one contains questions by the Board of Inquiry and participants, two contain a summary, and two are unidentified. The remaining cassettes include "Population Series " on population aid to developing countries, "Newsmark: for Export Only" on overseas dumping of dangerous drugs other items and two on tamoxifen. The two videotapes are "Assessing Your Risk for Breast Cancer" distributed by Zeneca Pharmaceuticals and the "Donahue Show" on Depo-Provera.
- National Women's Health Network website, First captured August 20, 2016; 1 website (single)
  The archived website of the National Women's Health Network (https://www.nwhn.org/) was first captured in 2015. Subsequent captures are scheduled annually. The website includes information and resources related to women's health; NWHN in the news; policy advocacy work; and the NWHN blog.
- 2019-S-0005, 1976-2015; 9.167 linear feet (11 containers)
  - Matria V. NWHN, 1997-2002 (Box 244)
    - Appeal Letter, 1997 May (Box 244)
    - Reactions to lawsuit, 1997-1998 (Box 244)
    - Suit/dismissed press release, 1997 December 1 (Box 244)
    - Martia v. NWHN notes, 1997 January-October (Box 244)
    - Matriav, NWHN - notes, etc., 1997-2002 (Box 244)
    - Matria's notion to dismiss, 1997 November (Box 244)
    - Matria v. NWHN - Motion for Sanctions, 1997 December 2 (Box 244)
    - Matria v. NWHN - NWHN's Motion to dismiss, 1997 April 4 (Box 244)
    - Matria v. NWHN Matria's complaint, 1997 January 28 (Box 244)
  - Terbutaline, 1992-2011 (Box 244)
    - FDA terbutaline pump letter, 1997 November (Box 244)
    - NWHN petition to FDA, 1996 (Box 244)
    - Terbutaline contacts, 2011 (Box 244)
    - Terbutaline James Reichman citizen petition 2008 FDA response, 2011 (Box 244)
    - NWHN correspondence with James Reichmann re: civilian petition, 2008 (Box 244)
    - Calls from women regarding pumps, 1996-2000 (Box 244)
    - Terbutaline counter petition, 1998 (Box 244)
    - Press coverage about Terbutaline -- Clinical trial / FDA hearing, 1992-1993 (Box 244)
    - Tocos (Matria) promotion of pump, 1992 (Box 244)
    - FDA Memos about pump, 1993-1995 (Box 244)
    - ACLU and NWHN press statements, 1997 (Box 244)
    - Pump press coverage, 1996-1997 (Box 244)
    - Fung Lam petition to FDA, 1998 April (Box 244)
    - Pro-Terbutaline campaign - articles, 1998 (Box 244)
    - Cynthia Pearson petititon to FDA, 1998 (Box 244)
    - Robinson (daughter death) Newsletter, 1996-1997 (Box 244)
    - Notes on pump deaths, 1998 (Box 244)
    - Kelly Crawford v. Goodman & Beatty, 1996-2000 (Box 244)
    - FDA Adverse Terbutaline reaction files, 1996 (Box 244)
    - "Ritodrine" and "Terbutaline" floppy disks -- adverse reaction outcome, 1996 (Box 244)
    - Minimed Terbutaline pump instruction manuals (Box 244)
    - Terbutaline Campaign, 1993-2005 (Box 244)
  - Clearing House packets, 2002-2006 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Abortion, 2001 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Alternative medicine, 2003 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Autoimmune disorders, 2002 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Breast cancer, 2003 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Breast cancer and the environment, 2004 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Breast cancer risk factors and prevention, 2004 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Breast cancer environmental causes, 2004 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Tamoxifen breast cancer treatment, 2004 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Detection & diagnosis breast cancer, 2002 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Breast cancer treatment & recovery, 2005 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Breast cancer, 2006 (Box 244)
    - NWHN Breast cancer packet computer disc, 2007 May (Box 244)
    - NWHN Breast Implants: Silicone, 2004 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Saline Breast Implants, 2001 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Cervical cancer and pap smears, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Chronic fatigue, 2004 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Chronic vulvar pain, 2003 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Eating disorders, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Emergency contraception, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Endometriosis, 2003 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Female orgasm, 2003 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Fibrocystic breast disease, 2001 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Incontinence, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Infertility & reproductive technologies, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Depression, 2004 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Lesbian health, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Bias in medicine, 2001 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Menopause: Hormone therapy, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Menopause: Alternative approaches, 2009 August (Box 245)
    - NWHN Menopause, 2009 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Menstruation and menstrual products, 2000 (Box 245)
    - NWHN General nutrition, 2004 (Box 245)
    - Custom good nutrition packet, 2004 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Osteoporosis, 2006 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Ovarian cancer and cysts, 2010 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Pelvic floor health, 2006 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Polycystic ovarian syndrome, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Pregnancy & childbirth, 2001 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Sexually transmitted infections, 2005 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Uterine cancer, 2001 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Tamoxifen for healthy women, 2000 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Young women's health (Box 245)
    - NWHN Women & diabetes, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Women and tobacco use, 2002 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Norplant and depo-provera, 2000 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Vaginitis, 2005 (Box 245)
    - NWHN History undated (Box 245)
    - Helen Rodriguez-Trias Info undated (Box 245)
  - Board of Directors elections, 1976-2008 (Box 245)
    - Board of Directors nomination submissions, 2008 (Box 245)
    - Election - Applications, 2007-2008 (Box 245)
    - NWHN Election, 2008 (Box 245)
    - Election, 2006 (Box 245)
    - BD Election results, 2004 (Box 245)
    - Election, 2004 (Box 245)
    - Board Election, 2002 (Box 245)
    - Board election materials, 2000 (Box 245)
    - Original copies (statements from candidates) election 3 floppy disks, 2000 (Box 245)
    - Election, 2000 (Box 245)
    - ad hov H&E committee, 1999 (Box 245)
    - Election materials, 1998 (Box 245)
    - Pearson, Cynthia, 1998 (Box 245)
    - Election results, 1998 (Box 245)
    - Applications, 1998 (Box 245)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1996 (Box 245)
    - Applicants for Board of Directors, 1996 (Box 246)
    - Applicants, 1995 (Box 246)
    - 1994 (Board correspondence) (Box 246)
    - CAMS Tally, 1994 (Box 246)
    - NWHN Board Nominations, 1994 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1994 (Box 246)
    - Board applicants, not eligible, 1994 (Box 246)
    - Board applicants, eligible, 1994 (Box 246)
    - Intra board letters / memos, 1993 (Box 246)
    - Election results, 1992 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1992 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1989-1990 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections statements, 1988 (Box 246)
    - Board elections - Candidate resumes, 1977-1988 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections statements - written notes, 1986 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1985 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1983 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1982 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1981 (Box 246)
    - Nominations / Elections, 1977-1980 (Box 246)
  - Board of Directors Meetings and manual, 2006-2015 (Box 246)
    - Board orientation manual, 2006-2012 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2015 March 21-22 (Box 246)
    - Board Meetings, 2015 June 27-28 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2014 June 7-8 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2014 October 25-26 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2013 March 23-24 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2013 June 8-9 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2013 November 16-17 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2012 March 24-25 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2012 June 9-10 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2011 March 18-20 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2011 June 11-13 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2011 October 29-30 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2010 March 6-7 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2010 June 12-13 (Box 246)
    - Board Materials, 2010 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2010 December 5 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2009 March 21-22 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2009 June 11 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2009 June 14 (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2009 September-December (Box 246)
    - Board Meeting, 2008 March 15-16 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2008 June 28-29 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2008 October 4-5 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2007 March 16-18 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2007 June 9-10 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2007 November 3-4 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2006 January-March (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2006 June 10-11 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2006 October 14-15 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2007 November 3-4 (Box 247)
    - Board Meetings binder, 2006 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2005 March 19-20 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2005 June 18-19 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2005 September-October (Box 247)
    - Board Meetings binder, 2005 (Box 247)
    - Board Meetings, 2004 January-March (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2004 June 12-13 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2004 October 23-24 (Box 247)
    - Board Meetings binder, 2004 (Box 247)
    - Executive Committee meeting materials, 2003 January 11 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting materials, 2003 March 1-2 (Box 247)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 2003 April 20 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2003 June 28-29 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2003 September 20 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2003 November 9 (Box 247)
    - Board Meetings binder, 2003 (Box 247)
    - Executive Committee meeting materials, 2002 January (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2002 March 3 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2002 June 8-9 (Box 247)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 2002 September 15 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting binder, 2002 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2001 November 3 (Box 247)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 2001 September 8 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2001 June-July (Box 247)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 2001 May 18 (Box 247)
    - Board Meeting, 2001 March 10-11 (Box 248)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 2001 January 16 (Box 248)
    - Board Meetings binder, 2001 (Box 248)
    - Board Meeting, 2000 March 11 (Box 248)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 2000 May 6 (Box 248)
    - Board Meeting, 2000 June 17-18 (Box 248)
    - Board Meeting, 2000 November 11-12 (Box 248)
    - Board Meeting binder, 2000 (Box 248)
  - Health Requests, 2009 (Box 248)
    - Alternative surgical procedures (Box 248)
    - Contraception (Box 248)
    - Fibroids (Box 248)
    - PMS (Box 248)
    - General Health (Box 248)
    - Pregnancy (Box 248)
    - Breast cancer (Box 248)
    - Gyn health / Pap tests (Box 248)
    - Menopause (Box 248)
    - Breast implants (Box 248)
    - Osteoporosis (Box 248)
    - PCOS (Box 248)
    - Hysterectomy (Box 248)
  - Packets, 2012 (Box 248)
    - Cervical cancer & pap smears (Box 248)
    - Contraception: hormonal (Box 248)
    - Endometriosis (Box 248)
    - Fibroids (Box 248)
    - Hysterectomy (Box 248)
    - Contraception: non-hormonal (Box 248)
    - Menopause (Box 248)
    - Menopause: alternative approaches (Box 248)
    - Menstruation (Box 248)
    - Osteoporosis (Box 248)
    - Vaginal health (Box 248)
  - Grants received by NWHN a-p, 1978-2009 (Box 248)
    - ARCA Foundation, 2008 (Box 248)
    - Catalog for philanthropy, 2008 (Box 248)
    - Catalog for philanthropy, 2006 (Box 248)
    - Catalog for philantyropy, 2005 (Box 248)
    - Common Benefit Trust, 2012 (Box 248)
    - Common Benefit Trust, 2009 (Box 248)
    - Common Benefit Trust, 2007 (Box 248)
    - Common Benefit Trust, 2008 (Box 248)
    - Common Benefit Trust, 2006 (Box 248)
    - Common benefit Trust, 2005-2006 (Box 248)
    - Common Benefit Trust, 2004-2005 (Box 248)
    - Common Beneit Trust, 2003-2004 (Box 248)
    - Compton, 2007 (Box 248)
    - Compton, 2006 (Box 248)
    - Compton, 2005 (Box 248)
    - Compton Foundation, 2004-2006 (Box 248)
    - Nathan Cummings Foundation, 2008 (Box 249)
    - Everett Internship grant, 2008 (Box 249)
    - General Service proposal, 2008 (Box 249)
    - General Service Foundation, 2005 (Box 249)
    - General Service Foundation, 2007 (Box 249)
    - General Service Foundation, 2003 (Box 249)
    - General Service Foundation discretionary, 2003 (Box 249)
    - General Service Foundation, 1999-2002 (Box 249)
    - Goldman Proposal, 2010 (Box 249)
    - Goldman Fund, 2009-2010 (Box 249)
    - Goldman Fund, 2008-2009 (Box 249)
    - Goldman Fund, 2007-2008 (Box 249)
    - Richard & Rhoda Goldman Fund, 2005-2007 (Box 249)
    - Goldman Fund, 2001-2003 (Box 249)
    - Goldman Fund - Putting People First, 2001-2002 (Box 249)
    - Richard & Rhoda Goldman Fund, 1998-2000 (Box 249)
    - IBIS Grant, 2005 (Box 249)
    - Level of Inquiry Spring, 2009 (Box 249)
    - Lupro Proposal, 2008 (Box 249)
    - John Merck Fund, 2006 (Box 249)
    - John Merck Fund, 2007 (Box 249)
    - Ms Foundation, 2007 (Box 249)
    - Jessie Smith Noyes Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 249)
    - Proctor & Gamble, 1996 (Box 249)
    - Public Welfare Foundation, 2007 (Box 249)
    - Public Welfare Foundation, 2005 (Box 249)
    - Public Welfare Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 249)
    - PPFA grant to NWHN, 2010 (Box 249)
    - Public Welfare, 1999-2000 (Box 249)
    - Public Welfare Foundations, 1995-1997 (Box 249)
    - Public Welfare, 1998 (Box 249)
    - Rexall Sundown redress fund, 2004 (Box 249)
    - Rowe Family Foundation, 2009-2012 (Box 249)
    - Helena Rubinstein, 1997-2006 (Box 249)
    - Helena Rubinstein, 1992-1997 (Box 249)
    - Helena Rubinstein, 1978-1983 (Box 249)
    - Gerbode Foundation "Get the Facts", 1996-2002 (Box 249)
  - Membership, 1999-2009 (Box 250)
    - Porter Novelli pro bono work, 1999 (Box 250)
    - Memberhsip fees - reassessment, 2003 (Box 250)
    - Logo, 2003 (Box 250)
    - Membership Planning Meeting, 2008 (Box 250)
    - E-aquistion concept meeting, 2009 (Box 250)
    - Recruiting Younger Memberships Recommendations, 2003-2004 (Box 250)
    - Member survey & results, 2002 (Box 250)
    - Honor 30 for the 30th, 2005 (Box 250)
  - Development, 2005-2017 (Box 250)
    - Fall Fundraiser, 2005 October 17 (Box 250)
    - Strong Voices Strong Coffee, 2006 (Box 250)
    - Articles by / about NWHN, 2013-2014 (Box 250)
    - Appeals, 2012- 2017 (Box 250)
    - Vivien Pinn retirement event, 2011 (Box 250)
    - NWHN video, 2010 (Box 250)
    - NWHN 35th Anniversary, 2010 (Box 250)
    - Laura Eldridge book event (Box 250)
    - Atlanta Luncheon, 2009 April 29-30 (Box 250)
    - Development plans, 2003-2005 (Box 250)
    - House parties, 2005 (Box 250)
  - Communications, 1994-2017 (Box 250)
    - Communications weekly meetings, 2010-2015 (Box 250)
    - Website re-design, 2011 (Box 250)
    - NWHN Alerts quarterly reports, 2005 (Box 250)
    - Cleaninghouse assessment / WHV transition, 2006 (Box 250)
    - Clearinghouse stats, 1996-2004 (Box 250)
    - NN series on women's health movement anniversary, 1994 (Box 250)
    - NWHN Fact sheets Breat Cancer & Women of Color, 1997 (Box 250)
    - Clearinghouse Ad Hoc Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 250)
    - Press clips, 1996-2006 (Box 250)
    - Patient Centered Decision Making Pearson, 2001 (Box 250)
    - New financial procedures, 2007-2012 (Box 250)
    - Staff conflict workshop, 2006 (Box 250)
    - Staff meetings, 2014-2017 (Box 250)
  - Board Communications, 2012 (Box 250)
    - Meeting with Consultants, 2012 January 13 (Box 250)
    - Ad Hoc Communications Meeting, 2012 February 23 (Box 250)
  - NWHN policies, 1975-2013 (Box 250)
    - Office merger (Box 250)
    - Bylaws change, 1999 (Box 250)
    - NWHN Policy decisions, 1982-1999 (Box 250)
    - Policy Media Floppy Disk (Box 250)
    - NWHN Policy decisions, 1975-1982 (Box 250)
    - Personnel policies - revisions, 2010 (Box 250)
    - Personnel policies, 2007-2013 (Box 250)
    - Personnel policy, 1993-1996 (Box 250)
    - Policy + personnel manual, 1995-1999 (Box 250)
    - NWHN policy - Pass Through Money, 1999 (Box 250)
    - Telecommunications policy, 2005 (Box 250)
    - Fringe Benefits staff decisions, 2005 (Box 250)